Piotr Zakowicz ACMA

Mobile: +447766133218 Email: piotr.zakowicz@gmail.com
Address: 401 Casson Apartments, 43 Upper North Street, London, E14 6FY

Candidate summary

Piotr is a high performing management consultant with five years of working experience, having spent four years at KPMG's London Management Consulting practice and one year on a procurement internship at Mattel Netherlands. He has a BSc in Business and Management from Aston University and is a Chartered Management Accountant: a member at the Chartered Institute of Management Accountants (CIMA).

Piotr has started his professional career during his third year of university, which he spent working for Mattel, the world's leading toy manufacturer, in their European headquarters in Netherlands. Piotr's role was to assist with pan-European procurement projects, by performing spend analysis, helping formulate RFPs, negotiating contracts and supervising procurement projects from RFP to store delivery.

Following his graduation, Piotr joined KPMG UK on a Technology Consulting Graduate Scheme, where has spent his first two years at KPMG working on ERP enabled business transformation programmes, taking on a number of client facing roles including project management, testing delivery, data migration and solution design. On his longest project in the utilities industry, Piotr has been given the role of advisor to head of Testing and Solution Delivery, which has been a testament to his ability to learn quickly and has resulted in his promotion to Management Consultant, a year ahead of his KPMG graduate cohort.

For the past two years, Piotr's focus has been on Digital Advisory, where he works closely with clients as a digital strategy consultant, combining his business analysis skills with understanding of digital technologies to identify and design bespoke software solutions that best meet clients' needs. Once a project is commissioned, Piotr works with KPMG's agile software development team as a Product Owner, defining the product vision, translating business requirements into system functionality and liaising with clients and developers to arrive at a solution in a collaborative and iterative manner.

Piotr is currently looking for a role in either Digital Consulting, IT Advisory or Digital Product Management, where we could continue working with clients and development teams to turn digital technologies into business solutions, in either a consulting firm, software house or a technology start-up.

Employment Experience

KPMG Management Consulting, London, UK **Management Consultant, Digital Advisory**

Oct 2014 - now (2 years)

<u>Train Operating Company – Smart ticketing solution</u>

- Developed an idea for an innovative smart ticketing solution as part of a client digital strategy.
- Created the product vision and business case and obtained an investment of £1,000,000 from KPMG to develop as a software offering.
- Leading an agile development team of four to develop the product.
- Working with an ecosystem of start-ups to leverage the latest developments in iBeacon technology and other micro-location technologies in solution development.

<u>London Airport – Dynamic Gate Allocation System</u>

- Created part of a high level design for a logistics system for all major ground operations.
- Designed the business processes for automated aircraft to stand allocation.
- Created wireframes and worked with UX designer to develop a front-end design of the system.

KPMG UK - Pulse survey mobile app

- Acted as Product Owner in the development of a KPMG mobile app for pulse surveys.
- Developed the backlog, created a product roadmap and led product testing.
- Designed marketing materials and lead a number of client sales pitches.

British Building Society - Financial Reporting System

- Co-designed of a financial reporting system for financial, regulatory and MI reporting.
- Supervised data requirements consolidation and data sourcing.
- Mapped data flows from source to reporting.

KPMG Management Consulting, London, UK **Graduate**, ERP **Advisory**

Oct 2012 - Sept 2014 (2 years)

<u>Distribution Network Operator – ERP Enabled Business Transformation</u>

- Advisor to Head of Testing and System Integrator's Head of Solution Delivery during a major ERP system implementation project.
- Led the development of Solution Design and Delivery Methodology.
- Authored the Testing Strategy and Test Execution plans. Designed and delivered UAT workshops.
- Supported the deployment of mobile devices to 2,000 field staff by participating in the device selection process and recruitment of SAP mobile trainers.

International Leisure Travel Group - ERP Enabled Finance Transformation

- Worked with client staff to map as-is business processes into flow chart diagrams.
- Supported the design of system security architecture, by designing user roles and authorisations.

Mattel Holdings Europe, Amstelveen, Netherlands Global Procurement Intern

Aug 2010 - Aug 2011 (1 year)

- Helped manage multiple procurement projects across Europe.
- Liaised with suppliers; gathered and analyzed data for tenders, supervised and assisted suppliers during tendering, production and delivery processes.
- Supported negotiation and formulation of contracts and service-level agreements.
- Provided technical support for all active tenders through an online procurement platform.

Education and Professional Qualifications

| - | BSc (Hons) Business and Management, 2.1, Aston University, Birmingham | Jun 2012 |
|---|---|----------|
| - | Chartered Institute of Management Accountants (CIMA), BPP, London | Dec 2015 |
| - | PRINCE2 Practitioner, Axelos, London | Aug 2015 |
| - | Certified Scrum Product Owner, Scrum Alliance, London | Feb 2016 |
| - | KPMG Assessment Centre Recruiter, KPMG Business School | Sep 2014 |
| - | SAP Finance module, KPMG Business School | Mar 2014 |
| - | SAP CRM Service module, SAP Education | Dec 2013 |
| - | SAP for Management Consultants | Sep 2013 |

- Languages: Polish (native), English (fluent), French and Russian (intermediate)
- Software skills: Proficient user of Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Outlook, PowerPoint, Project)
 and agile design and development tools (JIRA, Balsamiq, Axure, InVision, Launchrock, Wufoo)

Personal Interests

Travelling, basketball, windsurfing, kitesurfing, skiing, snowboarding, tennis and reading – psychology, business and historical fiction.

References available upon request.